https://www.arizonanationalgolfclub.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
Indigo Golf Partners, LLC, its subsidiaries and golf courses are committed to taking measures to respect and protect your privacy. This privacy policy sets forth the measures we take with regard to how we use, protect and allow others to view your personal information.Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience at our managed courses, Internet sites, applications and online services (“Services”). This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Services to make your experience with the course easier. We will only process your Personal Data in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws.If you choose to disclose your e-mail address or other contact information through any correspondence, registration, reservation procedure, contract, or request for information, we may use it to periodically to send you information. If you would prefer not to receive such information, you can choose to opt out of the communication at any time by following the instructions in the e-mail that you receive or by contacting the course directly.Except as otherwise expressly noted herein or within the course of providing Services, we may share any information collected through our Services, including without limitation, your name, postal address, email, (and any other information we combine with that information) with our Indigo Golf Partners-affiliated companies, our provider partners and service providers, and with carefully selected third-party organizations and marketers of products and services potentially of interest to you.Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide you with a customized experience when using our Services and to make them more valuable to you. We also use the information we collect to help us and advertisers efficiently reach consumers who are most likely to be interested in particular products and services. In addition, we and our authorized service providers generally use other information that we or they collect about you to:Enable you to participate in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards;Provide you with special offers, promotions and information from companies within our corporate family, and select third parties in accordance with applicable law;For more information or to contact us, please call 1-866-589-7757, or write to Indigo Golf Partners, Attn: Privacy Policy, 12700 Sunrise Valley Dr. Suite 300 Reston, VA 20191.
